

OSCAR MARINO BELTRÁN DUKMAK

Master of Engineering

Business Administration
Industrial Engineering
Technologist

PROFILE

Master of engineering, Business Administrator and Technologist in Industrial Engineering, with more than 20 years of comprehensive experience in the supply chain of the pharmaceutical sector.

Proactive, organized person, with communicative capacity to connect with a diverse public, with analytical and systemic thinking, leadership with a strong achievement orientation in pursuit of challenging goals. Interested in supporting new professional scenarios with a passion for quality and excellence.

CONTACT

- (+1) 908 549 8122
- ombeltranduk@gmail.com
- www.linkedin.com/in/OscarMarinoBeltranDukmak

EXPERIENCE

Tecnoquimicas S.A. – Plant Administrative Coordinator.

2020-2022

Prepare and manage the execution of the budget, as well as ensure the competitiveness of the plant, through the monitoring and coordination of the production processes, and the efficiency of the support activities.

RELEVANT SKILLS

- Frontend: HTML5, CSS, Flask, Django, React and Boostrap.
- Backend: Python, MySQL and SQLite.
- Other: Git and Vba excel.
- Data analysis (machine learnin).
- Mathematics and statistics.
- Analysis and critical thinking.
- Advanced level microsoft office package.
- Intermediate level of English.

Planning and Purchasing Leader

2017-2020

Planning production and supply of it. Guarantee optimal levels of finished product inventory, without generating obsolescence or expiration. Be custodian and guarantor of the correct configuration of the Oracle manufacturing system. Generate and present management indicators to the Vice Presidency.

TRAINING

Master of Engineering

2018-2020

Pontifical Javeriana University Cali.

Buyer

2016-2017

Guarantee the supply of inputs for the production process, at the best price and quality. Search and develop competitive suppliers. Generate and monitor management and compliance indicators.

Business Administration

2008-2013

Pontifical Javeriana University Cali.

Planning and Puchasing Analyst

2014-2016

Timely release production orders to the plant, with complete and available supplies. Follow up the processes to guarantee the delivery of the finished product to the distribution center. Monitor the supply of the production process in charge of purchases. Carry out monitoring reports and generate management and compliance indicators.

Industrial Engineering Technologist

1997-2000

Colombian Center for Professional Studies.